Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents G
  - Gruyter, Walter de & Co. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1925 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - (Enc. of clippings about "Kultur und Rasse."), 1938 Jan. 14; 1p.
      (Enc. English preface to proposed new edition of His "Kultur und Rasse")
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - Gruyter, Walter de & Co. -- to E. Seler, 1920 Mar. 11; 2p.
  - Gsellius Buchhandlung (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 10; bill
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 22; bill
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 19; 1p.
  - Guenzel, Louis (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 16; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 May 7
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 2; 2p.
  - Guérard, Albert (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1941 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 16; 1p.
  - Guernsey, George T. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 9; 1p.
  - Guggenheimer, Ida (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1941 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 12; 1p.
  - Guidoni, A. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 18; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec.; 3p.
  - Guio? Tomaso? (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; postcard
  - Gulick, Luther S. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 June 4
    - From Boas, 1917 June 12
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 May 3
    - To Boas, 1917 May 29
    - To Boas, 1917 June 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 June 11; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 2; 1p.
    - (Enc: Proposed of organization of an International Bureau of migrations), 1933 Nov. 4; 1p.
  - Gulkowitsch, Lazar (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas
    - See Anon. to Gulkowitsch, L. Dir. of the Rockefeller Foundation, European office (Social Sciences), Dec. 30, 1935
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 22; 2p.
      (Enc: Forschungsprogram)
  - Gundlach, Ernest T. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 30; 1p.
    - E. Gundlach -- to Howard Wurlitzer, 1920 June 7; 2p.
    - E. Gundlach -- from Howard Wurlitzer, 1920 July 24; 1p.
  - Günther, C. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1912 June 19
  - Gunther, Erna (Box 35)
    See Spier, E.G. (Erna Gunther)
  - Günther, I.R. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 3p.
  - Güntter, O. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 12; 3p.
  - Gurley, J.G. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1917 June 4
    - From Boas, 1917 June 6
    - From Boas, 1917 June 6
    - From Boas, 1917 June 11
    - From Boas, 1917 June 14
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 June 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 1; 2p.
  - Gurovith (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 24; 1p.
  - Gürster, E. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 8; 2p.
  - Gusinde, M. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 16; 2p.
      List of brochures.
    - (Enc. with Ronciére, C. de la, Feb. 24, 1933)
  - Gutenberg-Haus Franz Franke (Box 35)
    - To Dr. B. Laufer, 1898 Feb. 3
    - To Dr. B. Laufer, 1898 Feb. 3
      See also Franke, Franz
  - Güterbock, B. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 1
  - Guthe, C.E. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 19; 1p.
    - C.E. Guthe -- from C.H. Danforth, 1931 June 29
    - (Enc. with Danforth, C.H., June 29, 1931)
  - Guthrie, William D. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - (Enc: Guthrie, W.D. to Dixon, R.B. Mar. 21, 1924), 1924 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: Sargent, J.G. to Guthrie, W.D. should be, Dec. 30, 1925- 1924)
    - Guthrie, W.D. to Sargent, J.G. Attorney-general Dec. 7, 1925 should be 1924), 1925 Aug. 5; 1p
    - W.D. Guthrie -- to R.B. Dixon, 1924 Mar. 21; 3p.
    - (Enc. originally with Guthrie, W.D., Mar. 21, 1924)
    - W.D. Guthrie -- to J.G. Sargent, 1924 Dec. 7; 2p.
    - (Enc. originally with Guthrie, W.D., Jan. 5, 1925.
    - W.D. Guthrie -- from J.G. Sargent, 1924 Dec. 30
    - (Enc. originally with Guthrie, W.D., Jan. 5, 1925)
  - Guthrie, W.N. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 17
  - Gutkind, E. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 11; 1p.
  - Gutley, J.G. (Box 35)
    - To Boas, 1917 May 26
  - Gutman, James (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 28; 1p.
  - Gutmann & Co. (Box 35)
    - See Cohen, Samuel, 7-7-36
  - Gutstadt, Richard E. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 June 18; 1p.
    - Gutstadt, R.E. -- to Badman, T., 1933 June 8; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Badman, T., June 15, 1933)
    - Gutstadt, R.E. -- from Badman, T., 1935 Mar. 11
    - (Enc. with Badman, T., Mar. 11, 1935)
  - Guttstaedt, R.I. (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p.
  - Guyot, Yves (Box 35)
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 31
    - See Boas to Hrdlicka, A., 1919 May 24